A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, 1903-1947
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series II. Files, 1903-1947
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1931 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1932 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Underhill, G.W., Notes, 1932 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1933 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1935 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1940 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Underhill, G.W., Report, 1941 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Dr. A.W. Drinkard, Jr., Director, correspondence files, 1928-1929
    - Box content list (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - A Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Allen, Dr. E.W., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Anderson, B.G. (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Andrews, F.S., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Applications, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - B Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Bailey, Miss Ilena M., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Bradford, J.H. (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Ralph M., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Burruss, Pres. Julian A. (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Byrd, Gov. Harry F., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - C Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Caldwell-Sites Co. (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Carson, W.E., Richmond, VA, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Cocke, R.P., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Combs, E.R., Comptroller, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Copley, T.L., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - D Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Dinwiddie, Miss Martha, 1928 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Drinkard, A.W., Jr., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - E Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Ellett, Dr. W.B. (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - F Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - Ferguson, Sen. S.L., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - Fogelman, J.B., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - Fromme, Dr. F.D., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 27)
    - G Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 28)
    - Giddings, Dr. N.J., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 29)
    - Grange 772, VPI, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 30)
    - Green, W.W., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 31)
    - H Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 32)
    - Hamilton, C.H., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 33)
    - Harper, J.N., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 34)
    - Heitshu, D.C. (Box 108, Folder 35)
    - Hofmann, F.W., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 36)
    - Holdaway, C.W., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 37)
    - Horsley, J.R., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 38)
    - Hough, Dr. W.S., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 39)
    - Hunt, R.E., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 40)
    - Hutcheson, John R., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 41)
    - Hutcheson, Prof T.B., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 42)
    - I Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 43)
    - Industrial Commission (Self-insurers payroll), 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 44)
    - J Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 45)
    - Johnson, Prof T.C. (Box 108, Folder 46)
    - K Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 47)
    - Koiner, Hon. C.W., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 48)
    - L Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 49)
    - Mc Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 50)
    - McNeil, R.H., 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 51)
    - M Miscellaneous, 1929 (Box 108, Folder 52)
    - M Miscellaneous, 1928 (Box 108, Folder 53)
    - Magill, E.C. (Box 108, Folder 54)
    - Meek, J.H. (Box 108, Folder 55)
    - Moore Lime Co. (Box 108, Folder 56)
    - N Miscellaneous, 1929 (Box 108, Folder 57)
    - National Research Council (Box 108, Folder 58)
    - Nobles, C.R. (Box 108, Folder 59)
    - O Miscellaneous, 1929 (Box 108, Folder 60)
    - P Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 61)
    - Pettinger, Dr. N.A. (Box 108, Folder 62)
    - Price, E.R., 1928 (Box 108, Folder 63)
    - Price, Dean H.L., 1929 (Box 108, Folder 64)
    - Printing Dept., VPI, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 65-66)
    - Programs (Box 108, Folder 67)
    - Q Miscellaneous (Box 108, Folder 68)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 108, Folder 69)
    - Reynolds, Dr. Ellen A. (Box 108, Folder 70)
    - Roanoke Cycle Co. (Box 108, Folder 71)
    - Runnells, Dr. R.A. (Box 108, Folder 72)
    - S Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 73)
    - Box content list (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Schneiderhan, F.J. (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Schoene, W.J. (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Sheets, E.W. (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Snavely, Dr. T.R. (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Starr, Dr. L.E. (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - State Farmers' Institute (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Stechert, G.E. & Co. (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Strawn, O.P. (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Strong, W.O. (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Supt. of Documents [U.S. Government Printing Office] (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Swinson, Carl R. (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - T Miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Thomas, Arthur H., Co. (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - U Miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Underhill, G.W. (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Dept. of Commerce (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - V Miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Vernon, J.J. (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - VA Agriculture Experiment Station (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - VA Seed Service Inc. (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - Wade, Chas. I., Treas. (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - Wilson, Dr. I.D. (Box 109, Folder 24)
    - Wingard, Dr. S.A. (Box 109, Folder 25)
    - Wood, Col. T. Gilbert (Box 109, Folder 26)
    - W Miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 27)
    - Wolfe, Dr. T.K. (Box 109, Folder 28)
    - X-Y-Z Miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 29)
  - Dr. A.W. Drinkard, Jr., Director, correspondence files, 1929-1930
    - A Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 30)
    - Allen, Dr. E.W., Washington, D.C., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 31)
    - Anderson, B.G., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 32)
    - B Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 33)
    - Bailey, Ilena M., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 34)
    - Bradford, J.H., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 35)
    - Brown, Ralph M., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 36)
    - Burruss, Pres. Julian A., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 37)
    - Byrd, Gov. Harry F., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 38)
    - C Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 39)
    - Caldwell-Sites Co. (Box 109, Folder 40)
    - Cocke, R.P., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 41)
    - Combs, E.R., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 42)
    - Copley, T.L., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 43)
    - D Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 44)
    - Dinwiddie, Martha, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 45)
    - Drinkard, AW., Jr., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 46)
    - E Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 47)
    - Evans, Dr. Walter, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 48)
    - F Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 49)
    - Ferguson, S.L., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 50)
    - Fletcher, Dr. S.W., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 51)
    - Fogleman, J.B., Asst. Treasurer, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 52)
    - Fromme, Dr. F.D., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 53)
    - G Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 54)
    - Garnett, W.E., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 55)
    - Green, W.W., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 56)
    - H Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 57)
    - Hamilton, C.H., 1929-1930 (Box 109, Folder 58)
    - Box content list (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Heitshu, D.C., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Hofmann, Fred W., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Holdaway, C.W., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Horsley, J.R., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Hough, Dr. W.S., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Hunt, R.E., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Hurt, R.H., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Hutcheson, Jno. R., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Hutcheson, T.B., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - I Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Industrial Commission, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - J Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Johnson, Prof. T.C., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - K Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Koiner, G.W., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - L Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Lupton Orchard Service, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - M Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Mc Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - McCall, Dr. A.G., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - McCue, C. Purcell, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - McNeil, R.H., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Meek, J.H., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Merriman, F.J., Atlanta, GA, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Miller, E.C., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - N Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - O Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - P Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - Patteson, George W., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 30)
    - Perkins, W.R., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 31)
    - Pettinger, Dr. N.A., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 32)
    - Programs, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 33)
    - Price, Dean H.L., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 34)
    - Q Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 35)
    - R Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 36)
    - Runnels, Dr. R A., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 37)
    - S Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 38)
    - Schoene, W.J., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 39)
    - Sheets, E.W., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 40)
    - Strawn, O.P., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 41)
    - Strong, W.O., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 42)
    - Supt. of Documents, 1927-1931 (Box 110, Folder 43)
    - T Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 44)
    - Taylor, Prof C.G., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 45)
    - Thomas, Arthur H., Co., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 46)
    - U Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 47)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 48)
    - U.S. Dept. of Commerce, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 49)
    - V Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 50)
    - VAES-Staff Corresp., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 51)
    - Vernon, J.J., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 52)
    - W Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 53)
    - Wade, C.I., Treas., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 54)
    - Wilson, Dr. I.D., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 55)
    - Wingard, Dr. S.A., 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 56)
    - Wolfe, Dr. T.K. (Box 110, Folder 57)
    - Wood, Col. T. Gilbert, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 58)
    - X-Y-Z Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 110, Folder 59)
  - Virginia Sawmill & Logging Exposition posters, 1961 (Box 110, Folder 60)
  - Piedmont - N.A. Eaton, Jr., 1930 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1931 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1935 (Box 111, Folder 3-4)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1935 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1936 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1937 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1938 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1939 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1940 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1941 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1942 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1946 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1947 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Piedmont Field Lab, 1948 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Dr. A.W. Drinkard, Jr., Director, correspondence files, 1930-1931
    - Anderson, B.G., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Apple Storage - Bibliography (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Applications, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Appomattox Exp. Orchard, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - B Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Bailey, Ilena M., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Ballinger, Roy A, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Batten, E.T., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Blair, Chas. J., Jr., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Bradford, J.H., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Brown, Ralph M., 1930 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Bryant, Dr. Reece L., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Burruss, Dr. Julian A., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Byrd, Hon. H.F. (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - C Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Caldwell-Sites Co., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Cocke, R.P., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Combs, E.R., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Copley, T.L., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Staff, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - D Miscellaneous (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Drinkard, Dr. A.W., Jr., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - E Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Evans, Dr. Walter H., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - F Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - Farmers' Institute Program, 1931 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Ferguson, Sen. S.L. (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Fogelman, J.B., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - G Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - Garnett, Dr. W.E., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Gish, Peyton T., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Grange #772, VPI, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 32)
    - H Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 33)
    - Hamilton, C.H., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 34)
    - Hofmann, Dr. F.W., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 35)
    - Holdaway, Prof C.W., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 36)
    - Horsley, J.R. (Box 112, Folder 37)
    - Hough, W.S., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 38)
    - Hunt, Prof. R.E., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 39)
    - Hurt, R.H., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 40)
    - Hutcheson, J.R., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 41)
    - Hutcheson, Prof T.B., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 42)
    - I Miscellaneous (Box 112, Folder 43)
    - Industrial Commission, 1930 (Box 112, Folder 44)
    - J Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 45)
    - Johnson, Dr. E.P. (Box 112, Folder 46)
    - Johnson, Prof T.C., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 47)
    - Koiner, Hon. G.W., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 48)
    - K Miscellaneous, 1931 (Box 112, Folder 49)
    - L Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 50)
    - Lodewick, Dr. J. Elton (Box 112, Folder 51)
    - M Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 52)
    - Mc Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 53)
    - McCall, Dr. A.G., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 54)
    - McCue, C. Purcell (Box 112, Folder 55)
    - McNeil, R.H., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 56)
    - Maxton, J.L., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 57)
    - Magill, E.C., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 58)
    - Meek, J.H., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 59)
    - Michael, R.D., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 60)
    - N Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 61)
    - O Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 62)
    - P Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 63)
    - Patteson, G.W., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 64)
    - Perkins, W.R., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 65)
    - Pollard, Gov. John G., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 66)
    - Programs, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 67)
    - Price, Dean H.L., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 68)
    - Printing Dept., VPI, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 69)
    - Project Outlines, etc., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 70)
    - Q Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 71)
    - R Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 72)
    - Runnells, Dr. R.A., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 73)
    - S Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 74)
    - Supt of Documents, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 75)
    - Schoene, W.J., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 76)
    - Seitz, Prof C.E., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 77)
    - Sheets, E.W., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 78)
    - Soil Survey Mimeographed Letters by G.W. Patteson, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 79)
    - Southern Appalachian Study, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 80)
    - Strong, W.O., 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 81)
    - Student Employment, Returned questionnaires, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 82)
    - T Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Dr. C.C. (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, Arthur H., Co., 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - U Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Underhill, G.W., 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Dept. of Commerce, 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - V Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Vernon, J.J., 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Accounting Code, 1932 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Seed Service, Inc., 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - W Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Wade, Chas. I., 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Weather Reports at Winchester & Piedmont Field Labs, 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Williams, Dean J.E. (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Wilson, Dr. I.D., 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Wingard, Dr. S.A., 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Wolfe, Dr. T.K., 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Wood, Col. T. Gilbert (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - Young, Dr. H.N., 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - Blacksburg Report, 1933 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Blacksburg Report, 1934 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Blacksburg Report - R.N. Jefferson, 1934 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - Blacksburg Report, 1935 (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - Blacksburg Report, 1936 (Box 113, Folder 25)
  - Blacksburg Report, 1937 (Box 113, Folder 26)
  - Blacksburg Report, 1938 (Box 113, Folder 27)
  - Blacksburg Report, 1939 (Box 113, Folder 28)
  - Cox, J.A., Report, Blacksburg, 1936 (Box 113, Folder 29)
  - Cox, J.A., Report, Blacksburg, 1937 (Box 113, Folder 30)
  - Cox, J.A., Report, Blacksburg, 1938 (Box 113, Folder 31)
  - Cox, J.A., Report, 1940 (Box 113, Folder 32)
  - Cox, J.A., Report, 1941 (Box 113, Folder 33)
  - Cox, J.A., Report, 1943 (Box 113, Folder 34)
  - Blacksburg Report, 1942 (Box 113, Folder 35)
  - Blacksburg Report, 1943 (Box 113, Folder 36)
  - Bodenstein, O.F., Report, Blacksburg, 1943 (Box 113, Folder 37)
  - Blacksburg Report, 1946 (Box 113, Folder 38)
  - Eaton's Report Tables (Termites), 1932 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Notes, VAES, 1933-1934 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Notes, VAES, 1935 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Notes, VAES, 1936 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Plowing Tests Blacksburg, 1934 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Plowing Tests Staunton, 1934 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Soil Type Studies, 1934 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Agronomy Newsletter, First, v.1, no. 1, 1937 Dec. 20 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Letters & Balances, 1937-1938 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Librarian of Congress D.C., 1937 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Matthews, E.M., Chatham, VA, 1937 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1937 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Oriental Fruit Moth, 1937 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Pullman Telephone Co., Appomattox, VA, 1937 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - X-Y-Z Miscellaneous, 1937 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Chatham Tobacco Research Lab E.H. Glass, 1938 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Chatham Tobacco Research Lab, 1939 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Chatham L.A. Hetrick, 1943 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Chatham Tobacco Research Lab, 1943 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Chatham, 1944 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Root Immunity - Apple Trees, 1939 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Forest Insects, 1939 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Forest Insects, 1940 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Forest Insects, 1941 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - West Point Forest Insects, 1942 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Edge Growth Project Investigations, 1943 (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - Insect Investigations, 1944 (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - Chatham Research Lab, 1945 (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1940 (Box 114, Folder 30)
  - Edge Growth Project Notes, 1942 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - Jefferson's, RN., Notes, 1942 (Box 114, Folder 32)
  - Plum Curculio on Peaches, 1944 (Box 114, Folder 33)
  - Holland Substation, J.M. Grayson, 1944 (Box 114, Folder 34)
  - Holland Substation, J.M. Grayson, 1945 (Box 114, Folder 35)
  - Tidewater Field Station, 1947 (Box 114, Folder 36)
  - Experiments Published - Statistical Weighing for Age (Box 114, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 38-40)
  - Dr. A.W. Drinkard, Jr., Director, correspondence files, 1938-1939
    - A Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural Economics, U.S.D.A Bureau of, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Agricultural Engineering, U.S.D.A Bureau of, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Anderson, B.G., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Animal Industry, U.S.D.A Bureau of, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Applications, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - B Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Batten, E.T., Holland, VA, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Biological Survey, U.S. Bureau of, 1938 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Bobb, M.L., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Bradford, J.H., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Brown, R.M., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Bryant, Reece L., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Bureau of Entomology and Plant Quarantine, U.S.D.A Bureau of, 1938 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Burr, Charles G., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Burruss, Julian A. (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Byrd, Sen. H.F., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - C Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Chilean Nitrate Education Bureau, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Cocke, RP., Williamsburg, VA, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Commerce, U.S. Dept. of, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Comptroller, Col. LeRoy Hodges, Dept. of Finance, Richmond, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - Cunningham, Mrs. AP., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - D Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 25)
    - Dairy Industry, U.S.D.A Bureau of, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 26)
    - Division of Motor Vehicles, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 27)
    - Drinkard, AW., Jr., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 28)
    - E Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 29)
    - Eheart, James F., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 30)
    - Ellett, W.B., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 31)
    - F Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 32)
    - Farm Credit Administration, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 33)
    - Fippin, W.H., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 34)
    - Fletcher, S.W., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 35)
    - Fogelman, J.B., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 36)
    - Foreign Material, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 37)
    - Forest Service, U.S.D. A., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 38)
    - Fruit Products & By-Products, J.G. Brown, H.H. Hoon, Dr. J.G. Caldwell, W.V. Cruess, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 39)
    - Funchess, Dean M.J., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 40)
    - G Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 41)
    - Garnett, W.E., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 42)
    - Gish, Peyton T., Staunton, Va., RFD #3, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 43)
    - Glass, Sen. Carter, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 44)
    - Governor of Virginia, James H. Price, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 45)
    - Grantham, J.B., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 46)
    - Green, W.W., Bowling Green, VA, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 47)
    - Grizzard, Dr. AL., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 48)
    - H Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 49)
    - Hofmann, Fred W., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 50)
    - Holdaway, C.W., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 51)
    - Horsley, J.R., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 52)
    - Hough, W.S., Winchester, VA, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 53)
    - Humbert, R.L., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 54)
    - Hummel, B.L., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 55)
    - Hunt, R.E., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 56)
    - Hutcheson, J.R., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 57)
    - Hutcheson, T.B., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 58)
    - I Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 59)
    - Industrial Commission of Virginia, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 60)
    - Institute of Rural Affairs, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 61)
    - J Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 62)
    - Johnson, E.P., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 63)